It should really spring back and feel dry.
Another way to check it is to insert a toothpick in the center of the cake if it comes out with sticky batter then the cake is not finish and then you cake put that in for another 5 minutes and then check it again.
Now our cakes are done.
If you have cooling racks place them on the cooling rack.
Now it's time to frost our cakes.
You have to make sure that the cakes are completely cool before you start because if they are even a little warm it is going to melt your frosting and you will just have a mess.
First we want to have a nice hat box shape cake.
We are going to take off this cakes they are a little to round we are going to take off the top.
A shredded knife is the best thing to use for that and we would just nice and horizontally trim off the top of that cake.
This is a good treat for the kids, they would all want that top of the cake.
Okay.